Yeah,
I'm ready to hunt.
So tell me, what do I have to dio?
You want them to regret looking down on you, Then speak to them in their language?
Killed three saw tubes to ravages in a stalker.
Deliver their trophies directly to a cease.
That should shut them all up.
So if I do that, you'll sponsor me.
I'll consider it
minus.
Do you know
mhm waste of time.
Please wear
only the finest goods here.
See for yourself.
That must be the spire.
It's huge.
Yeah,
yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Okay.
Always stay bright.
Always stay alert.
That's what I say.
Don't pass up these goods saying, I promise.
Don't pass up on me.
Don't pass up these goods.
You'll like what I have for sale.
I promise.
Won't find better.
Wears price.
You like what I have for sale?
I promise
you.
Look, you'll regret not stopping when you're in the thick of it.
I've got all the best goods here,
but a crooked These won't cost you a shard.
Just something
good.
Camera.
Mind your business out.
I've got good.
Only the finest good pair see for you.
Find good there.
Got all the best.
Good.
Hard.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Just standing away from now.
Mhm.
Right.
Okay.
Another day passing.
Yes.
Come on.
Hello?
Yeah,
Yeah.
Fascinating.
If they weren't looking for me,
You know what you just told me,
You know,
and everything.
You
This is
pass the test.
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah.
Mhm.
Just
it also.
Yeah.
There's something
medical.
Just
Oh,
yeah.
Well,
sure.
Yeah.
Please.
Have you?
Yeah.
Just
hot.
Okay.
Yeah.
Low and quiet.
Does it?
Yeah.
Have a good week.
Okay.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Okay.
It's
okay.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's what's what's what.
Yeah.
Calm.
Yeah,
of
of course.
Start.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Cool.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
So
yeah.
Yeah.
He quiet now.
Public
six.
Here.
Yes.
Yeah,
Pandey.
I mean,
okay,
okay.
Time.
Oh, yeah,
Yeah.
It was
mhm.
I can get out of this.
Mhm.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Back to your business.
More.
Okay.
Fuck.
Here they come.
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Mhm Again?
Yes.
More.
Oh,
keep that for later.
Okay.
I'll shake it out later.
Yeah,
Okay.
Yeah.
Mhm.
No.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah,
yeah,
yes, Yeah.
Come on.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah
which
Okay,
that's right.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Okay.
Okay
about this stuff.
Sorry.
Thanks.
I think,
along with
Yeah.
Okay.
No,
thank you.
Yeah.
Do you?
Mhm.
Can't be too prepared.
Sure.
Okay,
That's not what I imagine,
But it's decent work keeping the city safe.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
That was worth it.
Mhm.
Yeah.
The director, Director, Director, Director.
We're
get it while I can.
Yeah,
we?
Mm hmm.
What happened?
Yeah.
Okay.
Just long stopped.
Louis.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
E a kind of a fight.
Uh huh.
Mhm.
Okay.
Oh,
so
no,
I see.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah
to
Okay.
Yeah.
No.
Nutritious.
The,
I think.
Yeah,
Right.
Okay.
Thank you for coming in
anyway.
You?
Yeah.
E expected.
Okay.
Do you want to interview you
people?
Yeah.
Okay.
Me?
You find him?
They just moments.
Great.
This now
from
It's not just
before you go.
You
Let's get on with it.
Mhm
Okay
from
Yeah.
Yes,
I'm looking right.
Find it?
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
You hear a brother?
That's right.
It's
Yeah.
Where is he?
Cohen now?
I don't know it.
She left grave in but she would find a way to bring me down.
But I did hear a report from the garrison of Lonesome Rock that a young woman had been abducted by bandits.
Might have.
This must be once, um, rock.
If it's a trap, I might need to go in Quiet.
I'm so well bored with being bored.
I'm bored with you talking about.
He was like an ordinary outpost.
I'm bored with you complaining about me being bored.
Better look around.
I wasn't complaining about being bored.
I was complaining about your complaining.
Well, now I'm complaining about your complaining.
If you two don't shut up, I'm going to complain to Zaid, and then things will get ugly.
Mhm.
We're chains in the cart.
Hold Outlander.
What are you doing here?
Hunting.
I've been tracking a saw tooth for the better part of a day.
Well, you must have lost the sun because we haven't seen any round here.
Now, be on your way and quickly
she's snooping around.
Rapper up a tired down boys.
Oh,
I'm down.
good.
Let's see what sites hiding out here.
Well, they don't want to talk, so let's see if they're hiding something.
not just chains, man.
Nichols?
Yeah.
They were moving prisoners somewhere.
The tracks lead to that compound.
Maybe in a co is inside.
Yeah.
Yeah,
That Nora girl we got in the hole is nice and lean.
Don't get ideas.
Day says hands off for a better price at auction.
Sounds like Niko is here.
And I'm gonna have to cut through these guards to get to her.
Yeah,
you can see them.
They can't see you.
Yes.
Mhm.
Yeah,
Nothing.
Oh,
you can.
I see him.
Uh huh.
That's coming.
Yeah.
Please help us get out of here.
Prisoners chained up to be slave.
The slaves
talk to Nicola.
She'll know what to do.
Nicola Yon sent me.
Look, we can talk more once we get everyone out of this pit.
Yon sent you.
I don't believe it.
I guess one of his prayers finally worked.
You'll need a key to get us out.
One of Zeid's men should have it.
I've got the key.
I'll help the others.
Let's go.
You can.
I knew you were going to be trouble, girl, but you will make it worth our while.
In the end.
The end is now Zaid for you and your men.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Oh!
Oh,
It's
yes,
you can.
Oh,
yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh,
okay.
Thank you.
Step,
you gave him a quicker death than he deserved.
My father was a hunter.
He taught me Every animal deserves a clean kill.
How did Zayed come to run?
A ring of slavers.
All the scum you just killed.
They butchered for Z.
During the red raids.
The new sun can kick them out of the army.
But Side managed to lie his way out of trouble, then saw a new way to make a shard putting his grunts toe work here.
How did I capture you?
I tried to get him a day tower, but he caught me.
Then let me go so he could have his men grabbed me later.
And after Said he was gonna sell me into slavery Like the other poor bastards that came through here a week to week.
But he took his time, kicked me around whenever he stopped by.
Guess me trying to kill him hurt his pride.
He's been through a lot.
I'm fine.
Are you sure Zeid's dead?
I was ready to go through anything to make that happen.
And I did.
What are you gonna do now?
The others were in that cellar for months.
The more run down they got, the harder it was for Xavi to sell them.
They need food.
Rest and hope
I'll take them to Meridian.
Intend to them?
You're not even going to try to go back.
What about Young?
The Matrix won't let me back.
Even if they would, I wouldn't go.
They can burn for all I care.
As for yon, I know a way to get word to him.
I'll miss that runt, but at least you'll know I'm safe.
Time for me to go.
Look, I don't even know your story.
Must be a good one.
If they gave you the mark of a seeker, if you ever feel like telling it, look me up in Meridian.
I'll be there until the others get back up on their feet.
Until then,
thank you
for helping me cut this rot from the world.
I don't know.
Maybe now I can put side behind me and remember my father as I should.
Thank you.
Thanks again.
For all your help.
Yeah.
I mean,
yeah,
you